lee. mizzi

about lee

Having studied photography at degree level I soon found myself pulled towards digital creation and graphic design. Since completing a BTEC in design in 2009 I have worked full time as a web and print designer. I pride myself on my attention to detail, efficiency and possessing an original creative outlook.

experience

August 2009 - Present: Designer - ISA Media. Including online/print brochures and magazines, websites, apps and marketing materials. Managing clients and projects. Developing branding and publishing solutions.

May 2009 - Present: Freelance designer Includes ongoing work with 'Life Water' on marketing and packaging materials. Voluntary work for the charity 'Kiya Survivors' on print and online materials.

2007 - 2009: Visual Arts Technician - BHASVIC College. Specialising in photography & digital arts.

education

2008 - 2009 - BTEC Level 3 - Graphic Design City College Brighton

2001 - 2004 - 2.1 BA honours Photography Portsmouth university

software

I am extremely competent in the use of Adobe Creative suite, particularly Indesign, Illustrator, Photoshop and Premiere.

references

Available on request.

07725914086 leemizzi@hotmail.co.uk

www.leemizzi.co.uk